This is Millie.
She is sat at her desk feeling overwhelmed by the stacks of tasks she has to do.
She feels anxious,
she can feel the clouds gathering above her head again.
She doesn't know where to begin.
Her anxiety rises,
it all feels too much.
Her work feels unmanageable,
leaving her feeling stuck.
Millie has an idea.
She decides to use the Eisenhower matrix to break down her tasks.
She lists her tasks and puts them into categories,
urgent and important,
important but not urgent,
urgent but not important,
and not urgent and not important.
Now Millie feels more inspired.
She knows to only focus on the urgent and important tasks today.
That way she can build up momentum to tackle
tasks from the important but not urgent pile tomorrow.
Millie has reached the end of the day and has made great progress on a few of her tasks.
It doesn't matter that they didn't all get accomplished today.
Progress doesn't have a set speed.
As long as you're making progress,
that's all that matters.